Guide to the Stanford University, Provost's Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Office of Management and Budget, Series 4
  - Facilities files, 1960-1981
    - Quad 2, 1966-1983
      - 02-550 Peterson Laboratory, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - 02-560 Reprographic Services, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - 02-570 High Temp Gas Dynamics, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - 02-570 High Temp Gas Dynamics, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - 02-580 Student Services Building (Old Union), 1979- (Box 42, Folder 26)
      - 02-590 Building 590 (including the Nitery), 1979 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - 02-600 Club House, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - 02-610 Mechanical Engineering, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 29)
      - 02-620 Old Firehouse, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 30)
      - 02-630 Stanford University, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 31)
      - 02-650 Starke Student Publications Building, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 32)
      - 02-670 Butler Building (Mailing Services), 1979- (Box 42, Folder 33)
      - 02-914 Delta Upsilon--553 Mayfield, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Quad 3, 1978-1983
      - 03-10 Cummings Art Building, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - 03-50 Career Planning and Placement Center, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - 03-55 Clock and Bell Tower, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - 03-100 Hoover Tower Parking Lot "H", 1979- (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - 03-100 Hoover Fire Safety, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - 03-110 Lou Henry Hoover, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - 03-120 Herbert Hoover Memorial Building, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - 03-200 Green Library, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - 03-210/200 Green Library budget, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - 03-200 Green Library stacks, 1978- (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - 03-210 New Library, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - 03-400 Meyer Library, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - 03-400 Meyer Library flood, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Quad 4, 1973-1983
      - 04-50 Sequoia Hall, 1977- (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - 04-70 Center for Integrated Systems, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - 04-150 Serra House, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - 04-200 Ginzton Laboratories, 1978- (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - 04-230 Applied Physics, 1978- (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - 04-230 Applied Physics, 1973- (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - 04-230 Via Pueblo Mail Development, 1978- (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - 04-230 Hubert Heffner Memorial Library, 1977- (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - 04-250 High Energy Physics Lab, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - 04-250 High Energy Physics Lab, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - 04-300 Electronics Research Lab, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - 04-350 Applied Electronics Research Lab, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - 04-490 McCullough, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - 04-520 Varian Physics Lab, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 28)
      - 04- 520 Varian Physics Lab, 1977- (Box 43, Folder 29)
      - 04-540 Durand Building, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 30)
      - 04-560 Mitchell Building Earth Sciences, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 31)
      - 04-560 Mitchell Building Mechanical Systems, 1979- (Box 43, Folder 32)
      - 04-650 Roble Gym, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 33)
      - 04-700 Terman Engineering Library, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 34)
      - 04-700 Terman Engineering Library, 1978- (Box 43, Folder 35)
      - 04-700 Samuel Morris Way, 1977- (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Quad 5, 1966-1983
      - 05- General, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - 05- Center on Student Residences energy consultant, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - 05-10 Lagunita Court, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - 05-100 Roble Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - 05-200 Florence Moore Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - 05-300 Knoll, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - 05-350 Boathouse and lake, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - 05-350 Boathouse and lake, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - 05-350 Boathouse and lake, 1966-1973 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - 05-450 Kappa Sigma House--535 Campus, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - 05-510 Lake House, 1978- (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - 05-520 Lambsa Nu--658 Lomita Court, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - 05-530 Kappa Alpha House--664 Lomita Court, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - 05-540 Alpha Delta Phi--375 Campus, 1975- (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - 05-600/610/620 Robert S. Moore House, 1977- (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - 05-600/610/620 Robert S. Moore, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - 05-800 Golf driving range, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - 05-900T/910T MUsic Modular Building, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - 05-900T/910T MUsic Modular Building, 1977- (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Quad 6, 1979-1983
      - 06-40 Encina Commons, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - 06-50 Eating Clubs, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - 06-100 Branner Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - 06-200 Toyon Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - 06-400 Wilbur Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - 06-500 Stern Hall, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - 06-600/650 Manzanita Park and Laundry Building, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - 06/910T/920T Office of Development, 1979- (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Quad 7, 1970-1985
      - 07-? Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Center, 1984 Dec-1985 Apr (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - 07-? Nuclear Magnetic Resonance program statement, 1983 Oct (Box 44, Folder 29)
      - 07-? Nuclear Magnetic Resonance, 1982 Dec-1983 Dec (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - 07-? Nuclear Magnetic Resonance, 1983 Nov (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - 07-? Nuclear Magnetic Resonance, 1984 Feb (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - 07- Governor's Lane, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - 07- Medical Center, Animal Facilities, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - 07-100 Museum, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - 07-100 Museum South Rotunda II, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - 07-100 Dudley Herbarium, 1977- (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - 07-200 Chemistry, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - 07-250 Organic Chemistry, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - 07-260 Stauffer I, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - 07-270 Stauffer II Physical Chemistry, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - 07-280 Chemical Engineering Gazebo II, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - 07-260, 270, 290 Stauffer I, II, II fume hoods, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - 07-290 Stauffer III Chemical Engineering, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - 07-300 Medical Center, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - 07-300 Medical Center Ambulatory Care Facilities, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - 07-300 Medical Center Cardio/Radio expansion, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - VII Educational Resources Building (Medical Center), 1974- (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - 07-300 Medical Center Immunology Building, 1975- (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - 07-300 Medical Center Materials Management, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - 07-300 Medical Center Newborn Nursery, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - 07-320 Cardiovascular Research Building, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - 07- Cardiovascular Center, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - 07-400 Falconer Library Biological Sciences, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - 07-520/525 Sherman Fairchild Building and Auditorium, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - 07-550 Louis B. Mayer Cance Biology Research Lab, 1977- (Box 45, Folder 24)
      - 07-900T Physical Therapy Building, 1970- (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - 07-920T Psychiatry Clinic Building, 1974- (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - 07-940T Drug Interaction Temp. Bulding (SUMC), 1978- (Box 45, Folder 27)
      - 07-945T Stanford Hemodialysis Center, 1975- (Box 45, Folder 28)
      - 07-970T Koko's House, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 29)
      - 07-980T Orthopedic Research Module, 1978- (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Quad 8, 1971-1983
      - 08-100 Athletics and P.E., 1979- (Box 45, Folder 31)
      - 08-110 Daper Fieldhouse, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 32)
      - 08-200 Old Pavilion, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 33)
      - 08-300 Memorial Hall, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 34)
      - 08-300 Memorial Hall Advisory Group, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 35)
      - 08-350 Business Grad. School, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 36)
      - 08-350 "Pillars of Hercules III" sculpture, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 37)
      - 08-350 Business School/info. project, 1971- (Box 45, Folder 38)
      - 08-400 Old Steam Plant (band quarters), 1979- (Box 45, Folder 39)
      - 08-400 ROTC /Armory, 1972- (Box 45, Folder 40)
      - 08-400 Band Shack, 1974- (Box 45, Folder 41)
      - 08-500 Galvez House 200 Galvez, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 42)
      - 08-600 Frost ( Laurence) Amphitheatre, 1979- (Box 45, Folder 43)
    - Quad 9, 1975-1983
      - 09-General, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - 09-100 Plant Service Building, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - 09-110 Stores--330 Bonair Siding, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - 09-110 I.D. Mail, 1977- (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - 09-120 Credit Union, Stanford Federal, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - 09-190 Telecommunications Center, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - 09-190 Communications Modular Building (Breitrose), 1975- (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - 09-230 Fluoridation Station, 1977- (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - 09-250 Shell Service Station, 1975- (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - 09-300 Maples (Roscoe) Pavilion, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - 09-310 Athletic Complex, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - 09-400 Commisary/Food Service (residence halls), 1978- (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - 09- Centres Building (#546), 1975- (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - 09-500 Stadium, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - 09-920T CCSC--Little Kid's Place, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Quad 10, 1971-1983
      - 10- General, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - 10-145 Escondido Village Highrise Mirrielees, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - 10-170 Escondido Library--865 Escondido Road, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - 10-180 Escondido Community Center--845 Escondido Road, 1977- (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - 10-300 Bing Nursery School, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 20)
      - 10-300 Bing Nursery School, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 21)
      - 10-310 Tower House--860 Escondido Road, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 22)
      - 10-320 Hacienda Apartments--860 Escondido Road, 1971- (Box 46, Folder 23)
      - 10-610 Alpha Sigma Phi--585 Cowell, 1976- (Box 46, Folder 24)
      - 10- Escondido Pool, 1975- (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Quad 11, 1972-1983
      - 11- Row House general, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 26)
      - 11- Mayfield Avenue Recreational Facilities, 1975- (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - 11- CCSC relocation, 1975- (Box 46, Folder 28)
      - 11-150 Stillman House, 1973- (Box 46, Folder 29)
      - 11-170 Old Stanford Elementary School, 1974- (Box 46, Folder 30)
      - 11-180 Grove I (Lasuen)--572 Mayfield, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 31)
      - 11-200 Grove II (Mayfield)--584 Mayfield, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 32)
      - 11-240 Jordan Co-op--620 Mayfield, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 33)
      - 11-260 Durand House--634 Mayfield, 1979- (Box 46, Folder 34)
      - 11-280 Roth House--813 Santa Ynez, 1978- (Box 46, Folder 35)
      - 11-300 Delta Tau Delta--650 San Juan, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 36)
      - 11-320 President's Residence--623 Mirada, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 37)
      - 11-330 Hanna (F.L. Wright) residence thru maintenance and moving in Project, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 38)
      - 11-330 Hanna House, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 39)
      - 11-330 Hanna House, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 40)
      - 11- Sub Committee on Faculty Staff Housing, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 41)
      - 11-400 Ryan Laboratory, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Quad 12, 1974-1983
      - 12-10 Golf Clubhouse, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - 12-30 Lathrop Gate House--200 Junipero Serra, 1979- (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - 12-50 Hansen Labs storage, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - 12-70 Student Observatory I, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - 12-70 Student Observatory II, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - 12-150 D.C. Power Building, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - 12-350 National Bureau Economic Research, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - 12-400 Solar Observatory, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Quad 13, 1977
      - 13-40 Information Station (Palo Alto Drive), 1977 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Quad 14, 1967-1979
      - 14- SCIP & RLIN moves to Jordan Quad, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - 14-100 Central Steam & Chilled Water Plant, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - 14-110 Cedar Hall, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - 14-140 Redwood Hall, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - 14-160 Polya Hall, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - 14-170 Pine Hall, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - 14- Netlofts, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - 14- Vanderbilt Fish Collections, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - 14-620 Bleeker Hall, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - 14-610 Art Studios--Searsville Warehouse, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - 14-200 George Forsythe Hall, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - 14-200 George Forsythe Hall, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - 14-200 George Forsythe Hall, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - 14-200 Stanford Computer Facility, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - 14-900 Meyer-Buck Estate, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Quad 90, 1970-1979
      - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station--Marinostat Building, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station Hovden Cannery, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station--general, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station--general, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station--general, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station-- Facilities Evaluation Report, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Stalion--Master Plan, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - 90-110 Hopkins Marine Station--Loeb Laboratory, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - 90-140 Hopkins Marine Station--Monterey Boat Works, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - 90-909 800 Welsh Road--rental (Blood Bank), 1979 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - 90-925 PI Meson Medical Center, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - 90- Family farm road flooding re: Jasper Ridge, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - 90- Fundraising Jasper Ridge, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - 90- Hastorf Briefing Red: Jasper Ridge, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - 90- Morrell property re: Jasper Ridge, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - 90- Pinehill Subdivision (Frenchman's Hill), 1972 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - 90- Searsville Lake, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - 90- Searsville Sailing, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - 90- Shack riders, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - 90- SLAC--Pep Project, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - 90- SLAC Synchotron, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - 90- Syntex Buildings, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - 90- Webb Ranch, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Academic Program: Values, Technology & Society, Undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Administration: Annual Reports to the President, Undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Admissions: Admissions Office, Undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Admissions: attrition, Undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Admissions: enrollment, Undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Admissions: transfers, Undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Admissions: female, Undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Admissions: general, Undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action: faculty, Undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action: internal, 1972-1975 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees: committees, Undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees: general, Undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees: rosters, Undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Business & Finance: general, Undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Business & Finance: indirect cost rate, Undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Computing-Administrative: general, Undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Computing-Administrative: Subcommittee for Administrative Computing, Undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Computing-Ballots: general, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Computing-Ballots: Report -The Future of Library Automation at Stanford, Undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Computing-SCIP: general, Undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Computing-SCIP: pricing, Undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Departments & Schools: Art, Undated (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Departments & Schools: African & Afro-American Studies, Undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Departments & Schools: Chemistry, Undated (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Departments & Schools: Communications, Undated (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Departmants & Schools: Earth Sciences, Undated (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Departments & Schools: Economics, Undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Departments & Schools: Education, Undated (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Departments & Schools: Engineering, Undated (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Departments & Schools: Food Research, Undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Departments & Schools: German, Undated (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Departments & Schools: Graduate School of Business, Undated (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Departments & Schools: History, Undated (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Departments & Schools: Humanities & Sciences, Undated (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Departments & Schools: Industrial Engineering, Undated (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Departments & Schools: Law, Undated (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Departments & Schools: Linguistics, Undated (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Departments & Schools: Mathematics, Undated (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Departments & Schools: Medicine, Undated (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Departments & Schools: Physics, Undated (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Departments & Schools: Political Science, Undated (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Departments & Schools: Spanish & Portuguese, Undated (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Facilities: Audio Visual, Undated (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Facilities: Energy - general, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Facilities: Faculty Club, Undated (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Facilities: general, Undated (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Facilities: Health & Safety, Undated (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Facilities: libraries, Undated (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Filcilities: plant services, Undated (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Facilities: space, Undated (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Facilities: telephone, Undated (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Fellow programs: Chicano Felllows, Undated (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Fellows: Public Affairs Fellowship Program, Undated (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Financial Aid: California State Scholarship and Loan Association, Undated (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Financial Aid: Deferred Payment Plan, Undated (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Financial Aid: policies (rationale and planning), Undated (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Financial Aid: Student Loan Program (general), Undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising: General Secretary's Office, Undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising: Gifts Project, Undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising: gifts, Undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Information exchange: questionnaires (external), Undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Information exchange: inquiries (general), Undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Legal: privacy, Undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Minority Affairs: general, Undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Minority Affairs: programs (general), Undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous: personal (R .F. Bacchetti), Undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous: quotable material, Undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Organizations: American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1975- (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Organizations: American Council on Education Commissions on Administrative Affairs, Undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Organizations: American Council on Education general, Undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Organizations: American Council on Education Minnesota cost analysis, 1976- (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Organizations: Association of Independent California Colleges and Universities (AICCU), Undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Organizations: Carnegie Comission on Higher Education, Undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Organizations: Carnegie Council for Policy Studies in Higher Education (general), Undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Organizations: CoFHE - Committees Policy Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Organizations: CoFHE - dues, Undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Organizations: CoFHE - general, Undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Registrar's Office: 78 Budget, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Tuition benefit: E. Shaws, Undated (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Buckley Amendment, Undated (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - ATP Report: Summary of Calculations, Undated (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Columbia University: salary statistics, circa 1970s (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - HEW, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - HEW, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - AAUP questionnaire, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - AAUP questionnaire, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Club expense reports, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Budget letters, 1973-1980 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Education and Law budget letters, Undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Engineering budget letters, 1974-1975 and earlier (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Engineering budget letters, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Office of Development/Office of Business and Finance, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - School of Law budget letters, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Budget making, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Budget making, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Budget making, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Budget staff, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Budget meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Budget: Budget Group - Agenda 1976-77 for 1977-78 Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Budget: budgeting - LRFF, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Budget: budget making, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Budget: Operating Budget Guidelines - final working papers, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Budget: Operating Budget Guidelines - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Budget: presentations re: 1973-1974, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Budget: presentations re: 1974-1975, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Budget: presentations re: 1976-1977, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Budget: budget making, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Budget: Autumn revisions, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Budget: Autumn revisions, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Budget: year-end closing, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Budget: miscellaneous tables & charts, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Administrative structure: Registrar, Undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Administrative structure: Research (Admin.), Undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Administrative structure: Student Affairs, Undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Administrative structure: Student Counseling, Undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Administrative structure: Student Master File, Undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Administrative structure: Student Services, Undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Administrative structure: Summer Session, Undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Administrative structure: Systems Development, Undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Administrative structure: I.D. Mail, Undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Administrative structure: Inter Audit, Undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Administrative structure: Bechtel International Student Center, Undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Administrative structure: Judicial Council, Undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Administrative structure: Libraries, Undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Administrative structure: Management Studies, Undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Administrative structure: News Service, Undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Administrative structure: OASIS, Undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Administrative structure: OASIS (general introduction), Undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Administrative structure: OASIS (system description), undated (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Administrative structure: Ombudsman, Undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Administrative structure: Overseas Campuses, Undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Administrative structure: Personnel & Employee Relations, Undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Administrative structure: Photo/Repro Service, Undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Administrative structure: Planning Office, Undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Administrative structure: President's Office, Undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Administrative structure: Press, Undated (Box 36, Folder 25)